Deverify has been examining the different sources of information that we have on this.
Israel described the al-Shifa hospital as the main headquarters for Hamas' terrorist activity.
This IDF animation, posted in late October, claims to represent a Hamas tunnel system underneath the hospital.
But having been inside al-Shifa since early Wednesday, Israel's yet to produce evidence of the tunnels.
It has allowed the BBC and Fox News to film at the hospital, though only locations of Israel's choice.
This is what they found.
Israel also released its own seven-minute video, which BBC Verify has analyzed.
A watch visible in that video suggests it was filmed a few hours before the BBC arrived.
And this IDF video was posted, then deleted, then reposted.
This time, without a section referring to an Israeli soldier who'd been held hostage.
I don't know when this was used the last time.
Also in the video, we see a room with an MRI machine.
And if you zoom in, and we get some light over here, what you'll be able to see is military equipment.
The BBC was shown the same room.
And what we see in the two videos doesn't precisely match.
For example, there's one gun in the IDF video, two by the time of the BBC footage.
Israel has told BBC Verify this is because more weaponry and terrorist assets were discovered throughout the day.
And as always, an AK-47.
Israel also says its video is a single shot with no edits.
But this appears to be an edit.
We don't know the reasons for that edit, nor how significant it is.
The IDF, though, says suggestions it's manipulating the media are incorrect.
The IDF video also shows military equipment in other locations, though we can't verify how it came to be there.
And what we see in this IDF video doesn't equate to Israel's description of Al-Shifa as an operational command center for Hamas.
The US is using a different phrase, saying Al-Shifa was used as a command and control node.
That implies a much smaller facility.
And as Israel makes the case for this operation, let's consider the Geneva Conventions, the foundations of the rules of war.